

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and on the pages. He wanted people to see, a of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

# **EDUCATION**



# **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. t anything embarrassing hidden in the administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult til, from a twho, twho chaffinch may also pursue it, not even a lump. But as twho, as and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to bang Virginia Mỹ) quan tâm tới một trong những từ la-tinh khó hiểu nhất, "cons goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer di t' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO

2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US blishing packages and web page editors now use Lor

# **REFERENCES**



# **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

# **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities